The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
A Warrior...
You
will all
die here.
Die !
Kill him !
His physical body can withstand the celestial sword ?
Only my original body
will be able to fight him.
Scram !
Kill him...
Kill...
Attack together !
The invaders
must die.
No one’s chasing me ?
Weird...
Whatever,
let’s just run for now.
If I don’t kill this guy right now,
I definitely won’t be able to leave.
Invader, the punishment for destroying our tree will be
your death.
I will
grant your death wish.
Your sword
is too weak !
God Slaying Chariot,
let me see if you are
worthy of your name.
It's only a demonic beast ?
It will die !
This beast soul is too slow...
I don't have time for that...
Master,
I can’t hold on much longer.
Master, if you keep using me like this
my Sword Spirit will dissipate.
This tattoo power
is truly formidable.
You can’t stop me !
Help !
I don't need to stop you.
This beast
is too vicious.
This God Slaying Chariot
is really worthy of being called a celestial treasure.
But with my current cultivation
it’s hard to withstand the beast trap's spiritual energy consumption.
The God Slaying Chariot takes too long to activate...
In front of a 7-leaf Shaman,
if it doesn’t activate in time
I won't survive.
Mu Ye
Forsaken Immortal Clan
7-leaf Shaman
This Junior invader
was able to escape from my eyes.
He has some skills...
Half a month later
If the enemy finds me,
I’ll have no way out.
Junior invader,
this old man has been waiting for you.
With your lowly Early stage Soul Formation cultivation
you managed to kill a 6-leaf Warrior.
You must be well known in the cultivation world above.
What’s your name ?
Wang Lin
The artifact you used to kill the Warrior
is that bracelet of yours, right ?
The scent of a beast
emanates from it.
The exit is sealed,
you can’t escape !
Tell me the method you used to hide your presence
and I’ll keep your body intact
and plant a tattoo in you myself.
You will become my tattoo puppet !
You have quite a few artifacts on you, Junior.
That's a good sword.
This item carries a hint of heavenly power.
But this is the Immortal Graveyard,
tribulations
cannot fall here.
What a powerful pressure.
The cultivation gap is too wide,
I can’t wait for the God Slaying Chariot to activate.
Unfolding it, tearing it, or throwing it,
there must be a way to use this scroll.
This scroll
why is it similar to our holy treasure ?
Now there’s only one way to escape.
Although it’s extremely dangerous,
it is better than waiting here to die.
A spatial rift...
So what if you escape into the void ?
It’s easy to get lost in the void
and you can’t break space to leave from within
Where will you escape to ?
Immortal Graveyard
Void
This Junior actually has a treasure to traverse the void...
His identity must be extraordinary.
He’s the perfect candidate for my tattoo puppet.
This old man said
that I’ll leave your corpse intact.
What a powerful soul !
Instead of waiting for my spiritual energy to run out,
I’ll take the initiative to attack.
You dare to continue to resist ?
I'm just fighting to survive.
You want to kill the both of us ?
You overestimate yourself !
I have put the first tattoo on your soul.
Even if you don’t die
you will still become my tattoo puppet.
You got me good
but I’ll risk my life
to pay you back threefold !
With both the celestial sword and the beast soul,
even a 7-leaf Shaman
may not escape unscathed.
I reached the 7-leaf stage
by understanding this tattoo.
Junior,
now that you have seen this tattoo,
you can die in peace !
To think my tattoos have been damaged to this extent...
You fight like a cornered beast !
The tattoo seed I planted in you
is impossible to dissociate from your soul
unless your cultivation
surpasses mine !
The rate of absorption is growing...
What is most important right now
is removing this tattoo.
Once my Origin Soul is completely enveloped by it,
I will become a tattoo puppet.
The tattoo spreads from the plant on my brow...
The plant...?
Wood element !
Heaven Defying Bead !
Since the tattoo is a plant,
as it’s wood element
it can be absorbed by the Heaven Defying Bead.
This gamble
is my only chance.
Under the influence of the tattoo
he can still control his artifacts
and hold on for this long !
It worked !
With these pills and top-grade spirit stones,
I should be able to hold on until he exhausts himself.
Why does this Junior have so many artifacts ?
He even has something that can remove the tattoo seed !
Thanks to Senior’s guidance
Junior has mastered the star compass’s teleportation ability.
He completely removed the tattoo seed
and maintained this speed for months.
That Junior has endless treasures...
If I keep chasing him
I’m afraid my tattoo power will be exhausted.
Forget it.
No longer going to chase ?
10 days later
You’re courting death !
My tattoo power won't hold for long.
Junior,
get the hell out of here !
If you keep following me
don’t blame this old man for taking your life !
4 months later
Wang Lin,
aren't you done yet ?
Thanks to Senior,
Junior can use this rare occasion
to refine his artifact mastery.
Apart from the rift we came from
there’s no other way out.
You are
trapped here !
This old man will send you to hell,
you have no way out !
No !!!
Now I can’t leave this place
and you cannot leave either.
This old man won’t let you go !!!
A madman,
you’re a madman !
I hope to borrow the clan’s spirit
to open a passage.
Ancestral Spirit Tree
Forsaken Immortal Clan
Master,
why did you destroy the exit ?
How are we supposed to leave now ?
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.